export const quiz = [
  {
    question: "Who invented C++?",
    options: [
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "Ken Thompson",
      "Brian Kernighan",
      "Bjarne Stroustrup",
    ],
    answer: "Bjarne Stroustrup"
  },
  {
    question: "What is C++?",
    options: [
      "C++ is an object oriented programming language",
      "C++ is a procedural programming language",
      "C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language",
      "C++ is a functional programming language",
    ],
    answer: "C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax of including a user defined header files in C++?",
    options: [
      "#include [userdefined]",
      "#include “userdefined”",
      "#include <userdefined.h>",
      "#include <userdefined>",
    ],
    answer: "#include “userdefined”"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is used for comments in C++?",
    options: [
      "/* comment */",
      "// comment */",
      "// comment",
      "both // comment or /* comment */",
    ],
    answer: "both // comment or /* comment */"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following user-defined header file extension used in c++?",
    options: [
      "hg",
      "cpp",
      "h",
      "hf"
    ],
    answer: "h"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a correct identifier in C++?",
    options: [
      "VAR_1234",
      "$var_name",
      "7VARNAME",
      "7var_name",
    ],
    answer: "VAR_1234"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of Constructor in C++?",
    options: [
      "Default constructor",
      "Parameterized constructor",
      "Copy constructor",
      "Friend constructor",
    ],
    answer: "Friend constructor"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following approach is used by C++?",
    options: [
      "Left-right",
      "Right-left",
      "Bottom-up",
      "Top-down"
    ],
    answer: "Bottom-up"
  },
  {
    question: "What is virtual inheritance in C++?",
    options: [
      "C++ technique to enhance multiple inheritance",
      "C++ technique to ensure that a private member of the base class can be accessed somehow",
      "C++ technique to avoid multiple inheritances of classes",
      "C++ technique to avoid multiple copies of the base class into children/derived class",
    ],
    answer: "C++ technique to avoid multiple copies of the base class into children/derived class"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the difference between delete and delete[] in C++?",
    options: [
      "delete is syntactically correct but delete[] is wrong and hence will give an error if used in any case",
      "delete is used to delete normal objects whereas delete[] is used to pointer objects",
      "delete is a keyword whereas delete[] is an identifier",
      "delete is used to delete single object whereas delete[] is used to multiple(array/pointer of) objects",
    ],
    answer: "delete is used to delete single object whereas delete[] is used to multiple(array/pointer of) objects"
  },
]